And now, The Transcredible
Exploits of Zapp Brannigan,
brought to you by
Bartley's Rocket Wax.
I wax my rocket
every day!
No one can save
you now, Leela.
What about
Zapp Brannigan?
Well, obviously, Zapp Brannigan could save you...
Zapp Brannigan!
So, Emperor Chop Chop,
once again, we meet at last.
Drop that space gun
or I'll shoot, like so.
Oh, Zapp, tie me back up
and ravish me.
I'd like to, Leela.
So, I will.
Shake it, baby.
Shake it like...
I surrender and
volunteer for treason.
Emergency summons from
the president, Captain.
Oh, it's you.
Just let me freshen up.
Computer, Captain's musk.
The long, dramatic corridor.
That's never a good sign.
Glove recognized.
Proceed, Mrs. Eisenhower.
Mr. President.
What the hell?
At ease, Brannigan.
What you're about to see
is highly classified.
Reptilicus,
hit the thingy.
At 0000 hours,
Planet X-3 was attacked
by a mysterious death sphere.
Magnify that death sphere.
Why is it still blurry?
That's all the
resolution we have.
Making it bigger
doesn't make it clearer.
It does on CSI: Miami.
They fought back with advanced military hardware,
but it was like shooting
BBs at Bebe Rebozo.
That poor, brave hardware.
The sphere then fired some
kind of hellish blackout ray.
It erased that planet like 18
minutes of incriminating tape.
Oh, I just wish
I understood why.
Why I should care?
Because the death sphere
is now on course for Earth!
My God, we're defenseless,
like fish in a barrel.
Options?
My instinct is to
hide in this barrel,
like the wily fish.
Then we're down
to our last hope,
a radical new weapon built
by a visionary scientist
I once dismissed
as crazy!
Let's see how crazy
I am now, Nixon.
The correct answer
is "very".
All right, Professor,
sock it to me!
Top-secret news,
everyone.
I've developed a tiny, one-man stealth
fighter that's virtually undetectable.
How undetectable?
It's right in front of you.
I find that...
to believe.
But how exactly is
this Happy Meal toy
going to destroy
a giant death sphere?
From within.
This ship should be able
to sneak, undetected,
through the sphere's
one vulnerable opening.
What vulnerable opening?
All death spheres have
one vulnerable opening.
Well, sure, but who's brave
enough to fly into something
we all keep calling
a death sphere?
I say Brannigan.
I say no.
I say me.
I say Leela!
I say yes.
I say no.
I say Leela, too.
I say yes again.
I say I shall join her.
But it's only
a one-man craft, I say.
There'll only be
one man. Me.
How would you feel if I rode rear
as your personal tail gunner?
Creeped out.
Then it's decided!
Are you sure I have to
sit in your lap?
It'll help us achieve
maximum thrust.
Ugh!
I made you some
trail mix for the flight.
Also, this picture,
to remember me.
You hold on to it.
I'll be back soon.
Activating stealth shielding.
Liftoff!
I'll roger that.
Does anybody else feel aroused
and jealous and worried?
I haven't felt much of anything
since my guinea pig died.
Death sphere in range.
Engaging
holographic targeting.
Activating the force.
Feel the entrance, Leela.
Destination on your left
in 0.3 miles.
Zapp to Leela. Look at all
that surveillance equipment.
We better whisper.
Switching to
pillow talk mode.
Look!
What are those huge letters?
V- GINY?
Doesn't ring a bell.
Hmm. I don't like
the looks of this V-GINY.
Does anyone recognize
those call letters?
Nope. It's not in the
Janeway's guide, either.
Deciphering that
ID code is critical.
I'll be in the chamber
of understanding.
This is it, the moment we should have trained for.
Holy...
Incoming yucky.
Firing pocket-rocket!
Don't panic, Leela.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
I hope this is
the control stick.
Captain's log.
We've lost control.
Addendum. Whoa!
And now, back to The Transcredible
Exploits of Zapp Brannigan.
Chapter Two.
The heat thickens.
Leela, wake up.
I can't face this
mysterious planet alone
without you or
someone like you.
Zapp? Zapp, wake up.
Leela, where are we?
We crashed on
an uncharted planet.
When I woke up,
I was pinned under this tree.
Can you help me?
If anyone can move it,
I can.
No one can move it.
Are you hurt?
No, but I'm so thirsty.
This space suit is making me sweat like a sow.
Me, too.
We'd better strip them off and
continue surviving au naturel.
Uh, I suppose so.
Here, we can cover ourselves with
these sticky, sap-covered leaves.
I'll try to avert my eyes
from your nudery.
You will?
What's the point?
You'll have to look
sooner or later.
Well, I promise not to
abuse the privilege.
For now, I'd better scout around
for food and water and help.
What a thoughtful and
considerate thing to say.
What the hell's
wrong with you?
I'm not quite sure.
Perhaps it's the fresh air
or severe head injury.
In any case, I'm off.
If you see any steaks,
that'd be good!
Why isn't Leela back yet?
Do you think she's okay?
How should I know? And how
come you never ask if I'm okay?
I'm feeling
a little neglected here.
Oh. Sorry. Are you okay, Bender? Shut up.
What difference
does it make?
When that death sphere
gets to Earth,
we'll all be blown
to manwich meat.
Well, I guess
it's time to indulge
in some end-of-the-world
debauchery.
Who's up for an orgy?
Yeah!
Yes!
Nah.
Maybe a Parcheesi tournament.
Belay that
Parcheesi tournament.
I've identified
the death sphere.
We may yet have
a faint hope of survival!
Still,
a Parcheesi tournament.
This is a top-secret
military satellite
launched by the air force
in 1998.
And this is a top-secret FCC
satellite launched that same year
to censor
indecent TV programs.
Like The Pimpsons
and Ass-o-rama?
Precisely.
However, the satellites
collided shortly after launch
and were never
heard from again.
I found the board!
Now I've simulated that
collision using shrapnel-vision.
Granted, all that
makes perfect sense.
But why is this death sphere
destroying planets?
That makes
the most sense of all.
Look at the planets
it's destroyed so far.
First came X-3,
the nude beach planet,
then, Poopiter,
and finally that world that can't
be mentioned in polite company.
You mean...
How dare you?
So, the death-sphere is
"censoring" indecent planets?
Indeed, and we're next if we can't
keep it in our collective pants.
Our sole hope is to persuade the people of Earth
to abandon
their smutty ways.
So, the orgy's off?
So thirsty.
Why couldn't a water fountain have fallen on me?
I couldn't find any water,
but the moisture in these fruit-and-nut
berries should sustain you.
Thank you.
I climbed perilously high
into the trees to pick them,
yet I saw no sign
of intelligent life.
Bummer.
Moreover, the crash
totally destroyed our ship.
So, we're stuck here
until someone finds us?
Alas,
that may never happen.
Stealth technology makes the
ship impossible to locate,
yet easy to stub
your crotch on.
Well, there's worse places
to be marooned.
Plenty of food,
mild climate.
It's a veritable
Garden of Eden.
It is?
Hello.
Did that snake
say, "Hello"?
No. We're both delirious from dehydration.
Just like Adam and Eve.
We can still save Earth. People
are sure to clean up their act
when presented with cold, hard
facts by rational folks like us.
The end is near!
Repent thy sins!
I'll thinks it overs while
I engages this $5 hooker.
Don't do it!
It's not worth it!
Okay, make it $3.
Yuck! I don't wants
no $3 hooker.
I'm going backs to
the adults bookstore.
Adult bookstore? I thought
this was the public library.
No. Pubic Library.
Zapp? Where are you?
Oh, God, I'm actually
starting to miss him.
Maybe you two
belong together.
We do not.
And you can't talk.
Come on.
It must be
an awful temptation.
Guess who just killed a
woodchuck with his bare feet?
I thought I'd whip
us up some shelter,
make this a little more
like home.
I do miss the Earth terribly. I
wonder if it's even still there.
Let's find out together.
I'll brave the ship's wreckage
to fetch you the telescope.
That's so sweet.
I'm just saying, is all.
I know my new plan is a long
shot, but it's the only hope left.
Well, now
I've heard everything.
On my iPod.
So, do you have a new plan, Professor
? And is there any hope left?
Indeed. We're here on
Earth's last unspoiled acre
to show the death sphere there's
still purity in the world.
Begin transmitting.
Commence purity chant.
Hey, I'm proud
of you, Bender.
Avoiding sin for
almost a full minute.
Bender?
Yeah, baby.
You're quite a dish.
Oh, yeah. Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no.
Bender, stop! Stop!
Quiet your riot. What's the
worst that could happen?
No! No!
Earth is gone!
We're the only two humans
left in the universe!
Oh, God.
I'm sorry, Leela.
Maybe this was
meant to be.
Maybe you and I were meant
to build a new world here.
We can avoid
humanity's mistakes.
Like the tuba.
Yes! We'll be
like Adam and Eve.
Only without the tuba.
And we'll beget little Zapp
junior. And Leela junior.
And they'll have
kids of their... Yuck!
Is that really what
happened in the Bible?
It's a sick and twisted
book of holiness, all right.
Then we'll write
our own Bible.
With less Sodom
and more Gomorrah.
Let's do it.
I shall become the mother
of a new world,
trapped here,
under this tree.
The tree of knowledge!
Look, it even has apples!
Ow!
Wow.
Come here, Adam. Partake of my forbidden fruit.
Thee will be done.
Wait. One more bite before we begin the begetting.
Mmm. Juicy.
Those nut berries you found were
so salty, I couldn't think straight.
I mean,
not to belabor it,
but they were as salty as that
bag of trail mix Fry gave me.
Exactly as salty.
Hey! Wait a second!
Uh...
I have a terrible
confession to make.
You see, when I first
went foraging,
what I actually found was the
smoldering wreckage of the ship.
Ignoring all danger, I charged
inside to liberate our provisions.
So, this is the
trail mix Fry gave me!
Yes. I exaggerated when I said
I picked it from the treetops.
I just wanted you to think
a little better of me.
Well, your motives
were good.
And we were both
loopy from dehydration.
Hey, wait.
You've been doing
an awful lot of urinating.
There's plenty of water.
You see,
after I selflessly
rescued the trail mix,
I braved the flames once more
in search of fluids.
Then why didn't
you give me any?
I thought it might help you
forget your intense hatred for me
if you were
a teensy bit delirious.
So, you let me dehydrate
while you washed down the trail
mix with imported mineral water?
Not exactly.
You see,
besides the trail mix,
the minibar also contained Doritos, beef jerky
and a generous assortment
of fine chocolates.
I wanted to offer you
the chocolates.
I truly did. But I was
concerned about your waistline.
Very concerned.
It's because
I haven't been exercising.
If only this tree hadn't fallen on me by chance.
Oh, dear God!
It was just after
we crashed.
I awoke first,
to find you trapped.
Leela! Leela, wake up.
You could've moved this grub-infested
log any time you wanted?
Well, sure.
But then I wouldn't have been
able to provide the loving care
you wouldn't have needed.
I'd leave you to rot
in this paradise,
if only the ship
weren't destroyed.
The ship's fully functional,
isn't it?
You see,
after re-trapping you
and before
feigning unconsciousness,
I paused to enjoy a cigar.
Though mellow and satisfying,
it did parch me a bit,
so I went in
search of brandy.
That's when my keen senses
detected the still-invisible ship.
So, we can
go back to Earth?
But there is no Earth anymore.
Everyone I know is dead!
This seems like a good place
to take a dump.
Leela? You're alive!
Fry!
But how did you
find this planet?
Well?
We're actually on Earth.
The ship's homing device
brought us back.
But I saw Earth explode!
I'm actually kind of
proud of this one.
You see, what you saw
was merely a simulation
I rigged up
using the ship's holographic
targeting projector.
The alleged telescope
was a toilet paper tube.
You said there wasn't
any toilet paper!
And that humanity
was annihilated!
My motives were pure.
I just wanted you to think
we had to save humanity,
so you'd be willing
to have sex.
Please say you believe me.
Yes, I believe you.
There must be something to steal on this island.
Hey, it's Leela.
Let's go home, everybody. At
least the world wasn't destroyed.
Yet.
People of Earth!
Hear the righteous word
of the mighty V-GINY!
The mighty V-GINY!
Seeing you frolic in
this unspoiled garden
gives hope that this world
may yet be redeemed.
Huzzah! The purity
chant worked!
Unacceptable
wardrobe malfunction!
I was referring
to Adam and Eve.
We're not Adam and Eve. You
see, due to a series of...
Consummate your union
or I shall destroy Earth.
Well, if it's to save Earth, I
guess I could take one for the team.
You what? Right now? But I
need a little romance first.
Maybe a vanilla candle
or something?
Commence intercourse!
Those giant guns are making
me feel sort of inadequate.
I'm not sure if I can...
Move it.
I've got to get home
and do laundry.
For God's sake,
censor it! Censor it!
Approved for all audiences!
No!
And now,
the spicy finale
of The Transcredible Exploits
of Zapp Brannigan.
That was a close call,
but we saved Earth.
Was it as good for you
as it was for the human race?
Oh, Zapp. Let's save
another planet right now!